>> who has been involved like on the good ones
the years have, as it were, stepped forward and wanted
take a bullet for the company, but everyone has it
as well as for various reasons then fell to the side
and think it's more comfortable if
Alexander takes care of it.
>> Mmm. But you were at a point too.
as well as doubts be cleared. And when that
now there are so clear doubts about what
has happened, the state does not want to take it up.
you kind of want to put the lid on it. It is
none from the state side that is
interested in giving them the target rise
or like spending more time without a man
from dialogic.
What do you value as high but as you
believes that the common man does not value equally
high?
What do you value as high but as you
then you must have what it takes. You have to
put in the time, you have to put in the hours, you
must sort of neglect certain things. The
can be about you not attending
summer vacations like you always have